roidbay.com 2018-10-23

# Privacy Policy | APKBucket

Here at APKBucket, your privacy is our top priority. On this page, you will find detailed information about how APKBucket (“we”, “our”, or “us”) collects, stores, and/or uses the information provided to us. If your privacy concerns are not addressed below, please use the Contact Us form or send an email to contact@APKBucket.com. 

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND USE

**Email:** Developers are required to provide a valid email address to create an account on APKBucket. Though we collect your email, it is safe with us. We do not sell or share your email with third parties. Occasionally, we may send emails regarding your account activities, website promotions and website news. You may opt-out of these emails at any time from your account portal.

APK Files: We collect APK files in two ways. First, Developers may submit APK files directly to us for inclusion on the APKBucket site. These APK files are stored on a secured server, and are tested for malicious code before they are made available for general download. Second, our ‘APK Downloader’ pulls APK files directly from the Google Play marketplace. These APK files are also stored on our secured server. As they are downloaded from Google Play in their original, unmodified format, we consider these files secure.

### COOKIE POLICY

“Cookies” are small text files stored on your computer or mobile device, designed to uniquely identify your browser when you view a website. We use two types of cookies on APKBucket:

**Google AdSense** We serve Google AdSense ads on our website. These ads store information on your computer in the form of a DoubleClick cookie. By viewing the ads as you browse the APKBucket website, you agree to allow Google to track information about your general activities and interests, and show you advertisements based on this information.  
Personally identifiable information is never collected by DoubleClick cookies. Only non-private information is collected and used. It is important to note that APKBucket does not have any access to the information collected by DoubleClick cookies.

**Our Own:** We store cookies on your computer to improve and personalize your site experience. The use of cookies enables us to recommend apps based on your preferences. We also use cookies to personalize Developer account options.

**Comment Policy:** As your privacy is important to us, we do not allow the inclusion of personally identifiable information in comments. This includes email addresses, full names, physical addresses, and credit card information. By leaving comments on our site, you agree to this policy. We reserve the right to deactivate user accounts that repeatedly violate this policy.

### PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES

From time to time, APKBucket may need to make changes or otherwise adjust this privacy policy in accordance with website practices. A “last modified” date, located at the bottom of this page, will accompany all updates. Please check this page periodically for any changes.

* * *

_Last modified on: Dec 09, 2016_
